<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on Vivek Kumar Singh</title>
    <link>https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/categories/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on Vivek Kumar Singh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 16:41:22 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/categories/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying OpenFaas on Docker Swarm</title>
      <link>https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/getting-started-with-openfaas/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 16:41:22 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/getting-started-with-openfaas/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post, I am going to talk about how to deploy OpenFaas on Docker Swarm. OpenFaaS (Functions as a Service) is a framework for building serverless functions with Docker and Kubernetes. To know more about OpenFaas visit this link.
I have already setup a two node Docker Swarm cluster running on cloud service provider Civo. OpenFaas repository contains a script deploy_stack.sh which can be used to deploy OpenFaas stack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with Docker Swarm</title>
      <link>https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/getting-started-with-swarm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Feb 2018 12:17:47 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/getting-started-with-swarm/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post, I am going to talk about how to set up a swarm cluster and some swarm basic commands. I will set up two node swarm cluster as an example.
I am going to provision two small size instances on cloud service provider called Civo. You can use any other cloud service provider like AWS, GCP, Azure or private cloud to provision instances. After setting up instances make sure that all instances are running on the same network and able to talk to each other.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Install Docker on Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/install-docker-on-ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2018 17:46:10 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.viveksyngh.info/blog/install-docker-on-ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>In this blog post, I am going to show how to install docker on ubuntu 16.04. We will install community edition of docker.
 Update the apt package index:
$ sudo apt-get update  Install packages to allow apt to use a repository over HTTPS:
$ sudo apt-get install \ apt-transport-https \ ca-certificates \ curl \ software-properties-common  Add Docker&amp;rsquo;s official GPG key:
$ curl -fsSL https://download.docker.com/linux/ubuntu/gpg | sudo apt-key add -  Verify the key fingerprint, It should match with 9DC8 5822 9FC7 DD38 854A E2D8 8D81 803C 0EBF CD88</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>